

Front Page

☑ Content should be centered
☑ Should have a navigation bar at the top
☑ navigation bar should resize/adapt to screen-size, not to that wierd thing..
☑ White Background
☑ content and layout scale/adapt to screen size.
☑ Contact form scales to screen size.
☑ choose either image or color for herobanner.
☑ find images for the three cards.
☑ images in tiles should not appear squashed/stretched.
☑ images should be sized something close to their display size
☑ Improve the look of the navigation bar. 

Resume

☐ White Background
☐ Summary Paragraph [b]still[/b] placeholder, fix this first.
☐ Content should be centered
☐ Should have a navigation bar at the top
☐ navigation bar contains links to Home, Projects and Contact
☐ Those links actualy work.
☐ navigation bar includes link to print out the resume
☐ navigation bar includes links to download a .doc and .pdf of the resume.
☐ navigation bar should resize/adapt to screen-size.
☐ navigation bar shouldnot appear in when printed out.
☐ footer should not appear when printed out.
☐ when printed out, entire page should fit on a single sheet of paper.
☐ When printed out, or viewed on a 'standar' monitor, layout should closely resemble that of the pdf and .doc version.
☐ Don't rank skills, just list.
☐ Give the skills listed for each project more breathing room.

Projects

☑ White Background
☐ Content should be centered
☐ Should have a navigation bar at the top
☐ navigation bar should resize/adapt to screen-size.
☐ each project has an image
☐ each project has a brief description
☐ each project lists 'skills demonstrated'.
☐ each project will have a link to a live view of the page
☐ each project will have a link to the github repo









